Guide to the Sterling Lord Papers MSS.058
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Print Materials, 1950s-2010s; 108 Linear Feet in 108 record cartons.
  - Subseries VI.A: 2016 Accretion
    - Daley, Robert. Man With a Gun (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - Daley, Robert. The Swords of Spain (Box 322, Folder 7)
    - Daley, Robert. The Whole Truth (Box 322, Folder 8)
    - Daley, Robert. The World Beneath the City (Box 322, Folder 9)
    - Danzig, Allison and Peter Schwed, ed. The Fireside Book of Tennis (Box 322, Folder 10)
    - Davenport, Diana. Wild Spenders (Box 322, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Dorothy Salisbury. Enemy and Brother (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Dorothy Salisbury. The Pale Betrayer (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Davis, Dorothy Salisbury. Where the Dark Streets Go (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Fannie Stearns. Crack 'O Dawn (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Davis, Nuel Pharr. Lawrence and Oppenheimer (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Deakin, Thomas J. Police Professionalism: The Renaissance of American Law Enforcement (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - DeBusschere, Dave. The Open Man: The Championship Diary of the N.Y. Knicks (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - Deford, Frank. Alex: The Life of a Child (Box 323, Folder 8)
    - Deford, Frank. An American Summer (Box 323, Folder 9)
    - Deford, Frank. An American Summer (Box 323, Folder 10)
    - Deford, Frank. An American Summer (Box 323, Folder 11)
    - Deford, Frank. Big BIll Tilden: The Triumph and the Tragedy (Box 323, Folder 12)
    - Deford, Frank. Big BIll Tilden: The Triumph and the Tragedy (Box 323, Folder 13)
    - Deford, Frank. Bliss, Remembered (Box 323, Folder 14)
    - Deford, Frank. Bliss, Remembered (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Deford, Frank. Bliss, Remembered (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Deford, Frank. Casey on the Loose: What Really Might Have Happened (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Deford, Frank. Five Stides on the Banked Track: The Life and Times of the Roller Derby (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Deford, Frank. Gut 'N' Run (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Deford, Frank. Lite Reading (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Deford, Frank. Lite Reading: The Lite Beer From Miller Commercial Scrapbook (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Deford, Frank. The Old Ball Game: How John McGraw, Christy Mathewson, and the New York Giants Created Modern Baseball (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - Deford, Frank. The Old Ball Game: How John McGraw, Christy Mathewson, and the New York Giants Created Modern Baseball (Box 324, Folder 8)
    - Deford, Frank. The Other Adonis (Box 324, Folder 9)
    - Deford, Frank. The Other Adonis (Box 324, Folder 10)
    - Deford, Frank. Over Time: My Life as a Sportswriter (Box 324, Folder 11)
    - Deford, Frank. The Owner (Box 324, Folder 12)
    - Deford, Frank. Sports People (Box 324, Folder 13)
    - Deford, Frank. The Spy in the Deuce Court (Box 324, Folder 14)
    - Deford, Frank. The Spy in the Deuce Court (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Deford, Frank. There She Is: The Life and Times of Miss America (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Deford, Frank. There She Is: The Life and Times of Miss America (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Deford, Frank. The World's Tallest Midget: The Best of Frank Deford (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - Dickens, Charles. The Chimes (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - Dickens, Charles. Cricket on the Hearth (Box 325, Folder 6)
    - Dickstein, Morris. Leopards in the Temple: The Transformation of American Fiction 1945-1970 (Box 325, Folder 7)
    - Doctorow, E.L. The March (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Doctorow, E.L. Ragtime (Box 325, Folder 9)
    - Dodson, Fitzhugh. The Carnival Kidnap Caper (Box 325, Folder 10)
    - Dodson, Fitzhugh. Give Your Child a Head Start in Reading (Box 325, Folder 11)
    - Dodson, Fitzhugh. How to Father (Box 325, Folder 12)
    - Dodson, Fitzhugh. How to Grand-parent (Box 325, Folder 13)
    - Dodson, Fitzhugh. How to Parent (Box 325, Folder 14)
    - Dodson, Fitzhugh and Ann Alexander. Your Child: Birth to Age 6 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Donnell, Susan. Pocahontas (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Donovan, Robert J. The Assassins (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Donovan, Robert J. Boxing the Kangaroo: A Reporter's Memoir (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - Donovan, Robert J. Eisenhower: The Inside Story (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - Donovan, Robert J. Nemesis: Truman and Johnson in the Coils of War in Asia (Box 326, Folder 6)
    - Donovan, Robert J. The Words of Harry S. Truman (Box 326, Folder 7)
    - Donovan, Robert J. and Ray Scherer. Unsilent Revolution (Box 326, Folder 8)
    - Dorfner, John J. Kerouac: Visions of Lowell (Box 326, Folder 9)
    - Dorfner, John J. Kerouac: Visions of Rocky Mount (Box 326, Folder 10)
    - Dornberg, John. Munich 1923: The Story of Hitler's First Grab for Power (Box 326, Folder 11)
    - Dornberg, John. The New Germans: Thirty Years After (Box 326, Folder 12)
    - Dorso, Richard. Thicker Than Water (Box 326, Folder 13)
    - Dossey, Larry. The Extraordinary Healing Power of Ordinary Things (Box 326, Folder 14)
    - Drew, Elizabeth. The Corruption of American Politics: What Went Wrong and Why (Box 326, Folder 15)
    - Drew, Elizabeth. Showdown (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Drew, Elizabeth. Showdown: The Struggle Between the Gingrich Congress and the Clinton White House (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Drury, Allen. Anna Hastings (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Duberman, Martin. Black Mountain: An Exploration in Community (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Duberman, Martin. Black Mountain: An Exploration in Community (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Duberman, Martin. James Russell Lowell (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - Duberman, Martin. Male Armor: Selected Plays, 1968-1974 (Box 327, Folder 7)
    - Duberman, Martin. The Memory Bank (Box 327, Folder 8)
    - Duberman, Martin. The Uncompleted Past (Box 327, Folder 9)
    - Duberman, Martin. Visions of Kerouac (Box 327, Folder 10)
    - Duffy, Clinton T. and Al Hirschberg. 88 Men and 2 Women (Box 327, Folder 11)
    - Duffy, Clinton T. and Al Hirschberg. 88 Men and Two Women (Box 327, Folder 12)
    - Dufty, William. Sugar Blues (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Dunham, Barrows. Heroes and Heretics: a Political History of Western Thought (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Dunne, John Gregory. Dutch Shea, Jr. (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Durand, Loup. Jaguar (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - Durand, Loup. Jaguar (Box 328, Folder 5)
    - Durham, Guy. Extreme Prejudice (Box 328, Folder 6)
    - Durham, Guy. Extreme Prejudice (Box 328, Folder 7)
    - Durham, Guy. Stealth (Box 328, Folder 8)
    - Durk, David and Ira Silverman. The Pleasant Avenue Connection (Box 328, Folder 9)
    - Eberts, Jake and Terry Ilott. My Indescision is Final: The Spectacular rise and Fall of Goldcrest Films, the Independent Studio That Challenged Hollywood (Box 328, Folder 10)
    - Eberts, Jake and Terry Ilott. My Indecision is Final: The Spectacular rise and Fall of Goldcrest Films, the Independent Studio That Challenged Hollywood (Box 328, Folder 11)
    - Edington, Stephen. Kerouac's Nashua Connection (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - Editors of the Wall Street Journal. The New Millionaires and How They Made Their Fortunes (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - Eisenberg, John. The Great Match Race (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Elbert, Joyce. The Crazy Ladies (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - Elbert, Joyce. The Crazy Lovers (Box 329, Folder 5)
    - Elbert, Joyce. Drunk in Madrid (Box 329, Folder 6)
    - Elbert, Joyce. Getting Rid of Richard (Box 329, Folder 7)
    - Elbert, Joyce. The Goddess Hangup (Box 329, Folder 8)
    - Elbert, Joyce. A Martini on the Other Table (Box 329, Folder 9)
    - Elbert, Joyce. Red Eye Blues (Box 329, Folder 10)
    - Elbert, Joyce. Return of the Crazy Ladies (Box 329, Folder 11)
    - Eliot, T.S. Collected Poems 1909 - 1962 (Box 329, Folder 12)
    - Emerson Jr., William A. The Jesus Story (Box 329, Folder 13)
    - Ephron, Nora. I Feel Bad About My Neck: And Other Thoughts On Being a Woman (Box 329, Folder 14)
    - Epstein, Edward Jay. News from Nowhere: Television and the News (Box 329, Folder 15)
    - Estes, Clarissa Pinkola, PhD. Women Who Run With the Wolves: Myths and Stories of the Wild Woman Archetype (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - Eyster, Richard H. and Christine Martin. Successful Classroom Management (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - Eyster, Richard H. and Christine Martin. Successful Classroom Management (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - Farichild, John. The Fashionable Savages (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Fairchild, John. The Moonflower Couple (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - Farell, James T. and Pete Hamil. Studs Lonigan (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - Farquharson, John. The Bell House Book (Box 330, Folder 7)
    - Fast, Howard. Agrippa's Daughter (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Fast, Howard. The American (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - Fast, Howard. Being Red (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Fast, Howard. Bunker Hill (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - Fast, Howard. Bunker Hill: The Prequel to the Crossing (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - Fast, Howard. The Call of Fife & Drum (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - Fast, Howard. The Call of Fife & Drum (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - Fast, Howard. Citizen Tom Paine: A Play (Box 331, Folder 8)
    - Fast, Howard. The Confession of Joe Cullen (Box 331, Folder 9)
    - Fast, Howard. The Confession of the Joe Cullen (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Fast, Howard. The Darkness Within (Fallen Angel) (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - Fast, Howard. The Crossing (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Fast, Howard. Departure and Other Stories (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Fast, Howard. The Dinner Party (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - Fast, Howard. The Dinner Party (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - Fast, Howard. The Establishment (Box 332, Folder 7)
    - Fast, Howard. The Establishment (Box 332, Folder 8)
    - Fast, Howard. The Establishment (Box 332, Folder 9)
    - Fast, Howard. The Establishment (Box 332, Folder 10)
    - Fast, Howard. The Establishment (Box 332, Folder 11)
    - Fast, Howard. Freedom Road (Box 332, Folder 12)
    - Fast, Howard. Freedom Road (Box 332, Folder 13)
    - Fast, Howard. The General Zapped an Angel (Box 332, Folder 14)
    - Fast, Howard. Greenwich (Box 332, Folder 15)
    - Fast, Howard. Greenwich (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Fast, Howard. The Hessian (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Fast, Howard. The Hessian (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Fast, Howard. The Howard Fast Reader (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Fast, Howard. The Hunter and the Trap (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Fast, Howard. The Immigrant's Daughter (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - Fast, Howard. An Independent Woman (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - Fast, Howard. An Independent Woman (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Fast, Howard. The Jews: Story of a People (Box 333, Folder 9)
    - Fast, Howard. The Legacy (Box 333, Folder 10)
    - Fast, Howard. Mirage (Box 333, Folder 11)
    - Fast, Howard. Moses Prince of Egypt (Box 333, Folder 12)
    - Fast, Howard. My Glorious Brother (Box 333, Folder 13)
    - Fast, Howard. The Novelist (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Fast, Howard. The Novelist (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Fast, Howard. The Outsider (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Fast, Howard. The Passion of Sacco and Vanzetti (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Fast, Howard. Peekskill USA (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Fast, Howard. The Pledge (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - Fast, Howard. The Pledge (Box 334, Folder 7)
    - Fast, Howard. The Pledge (Box 334, Folder 8)
    - Fast, Howard. The Pledge (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - Fast, Howard. The Proud and the Free (Box 334, Folder 10)
    - Fast, Howard. Redemption (Box 334, Folder 11)
    - Fast, Howard. Redemption (Box 334, Folder 12)
    - Fast, Howard. Sally (Box 334, Folder 13)
    - Fast, Howard. Second Generation (Box 334, Folder 14)
    - Fast, Howard. Second Generation (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Fast, Howard. Spartacus (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Fast, Howard. Spartakus (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Fast, Howard. Sylvia (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Fast, Howard. The Tall Hunter (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Fast, Howard. Thirteen New Stories of Fantasy and Science Fiction (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Fast, Howard. Time and the Riddle: Thirty-One Zen Stories (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Fast, Howard. Time and the Riddle (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Fast, Howard. Time and the Riddle: 31 Zen Stories (Box 335, Folder 9)
    - Fast, Howard. Tony and the Wonderful Door (Box 335, Folder 10)
    - Fast, Howard. A Touch of Infinity (Box 335, Folder 11)
    - Fast, Howard. The Trial of Abigail Goodman (Box 335, Folder 12)
    - Fast, Howard. The Trial of Abigail Goodman (Box 335, Folder 13)
    - Fast, Howard. The Trial of Abigail Goodman (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Fast, Howard. The Unvanquished (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Fast, Howard. War and Peace: Observations On Our Times (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Fast, Jonathan. Golden Fire (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Fast, Johnathan. The Inner Circle (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Fast, Jonathan. The Jade Stalk (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - Fast, Jonathan. Mortal Gods (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Fay, Paul B. The Pleasure of His Company (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - Fay, Stephen, Lewis Chester, and Magnus Linklater. Hoax: The Inside Story of the Howard Hughes-Cliffrd Irving Affair (Box 336, Folder 9)
    - Feinstein, Sascha. Jazz Poetry: From the 1920s to the Present (Box 336, Folder 10)
    - Felsenthal, Carol. Power, privilege, and the Post: the Katharine Graham story (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - Femina, Jerry Della and Charles Sopkin. An Italian Grows in Brooklyn (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - Field, Syd. Going to the Movies (Box 336, Folder 13)
    - Field, Syd. The Screenwriter's Workbook (Box 336, Folder 14)
    - Field, Syd. Selling a Screenplay: The Screenwriter's Guide to Hollywood (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Fishman, Ted C. China Inc. (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Fiske, Edward B. How To Get Into The Right College: Secrets of College Admisions (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Fiske, Edward B. Smart Schools, Smart Kids: Why Do Some Schools Work? (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Fitzgerald, Ed. A Nick an Inch: A Memoir (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Fitzgerald, Ed. That Place in Minnesota (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Fitzgerald, Ed. That Place in Minnesota (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Flach, Frederic F. Fridericus (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Flach, Frederic F. and Suzanne C. Draghi. The Nature and Treatment of Depression (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - Flaherty, Joe. Managing Mailer (Box 337, Folder 10)
    - Flood, Charles Bracelen. Hitler: The Path to Power (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - Flood, Charles Bracelen. Hitler: The Path to Power (Box 337, Folder 12)
    - Flood, Charles Bracelen. Lee: The Last Years (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Flood, Charles Bracelen. Love is a Bridge (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Flood, Charles Bracelen. Monmouth (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Flood, Charles Bracelen. More Lives Than One (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Flood, Charles Bracelen. Tell Me, Stranger (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - Flood, Charles Bracelen. The War of the Innocenets (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - Flood, Renee Sansom. Lost Bird of Wounded Knee (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Florance, Arnold. Queen Victoria at Osborne (Box 338, Folder 8)
    - Foote, Shelby. Three Novels: Love in a Dry Seasons, Follow Me Down, Jordan County (Box 338, Folder 9)
    - Forsynth, Frederick. The Devil's Alternative (Box 338, Folder 10)
    - Forsyth, Frederick. The Dogs of War (Box 338, Folder 11)
    - Fosburgh, Lacey. Closing Time: The True Story of the "Goodbar" Murder (Box 338, Folder 12)
    - Fosburgh, Lacey. Old Money (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Fowles, John. The Magnus (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - Frady, Marshall. Across a Darkling Plain: An American's Passage Through the Middle East (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Frady, Marshall. Southeners: A Journalist's Odyssey (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Frady, Marshall. Wallace (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Frady, Marshall. Wallace (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - Frady, Mashall. Billy Graham: A Parable of American Righteousness (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Francis, Dick. Break In (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Francis, Dick. Hot Money (Box 339, Folder 9)
    - Francis, Dick. Longshot (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - Francis, Dick. Reflex (Box 339, Folder 11)
    - Francis, Dick. Shattered (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - Francis, Dick. Wild Horses (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - Fraser, Sylvia. The Book of Strange (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - Fraser, Sylvia. My Father's House: A Memoir of Incest and of Healing (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - Freehan, Bill. Behind the Mask: An Inside Baseball Diary (Box 340, Folder 5)
    - Friedman, Thomas L. The Lexus and The Olive Tree: Understanding Globalization (Box 340, Folder 6)
    - Friedman, Thomas L. The World is Flat: A Brief History of the 21st Century (Box 340, Folder 7)
    - Friedrich, Jaqueline. A Wine and Food Guide to the Loire (Box 340, Folder 8)
    - Frump, Robert. Two Tankers Down (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - Frump, Robert. Two Tankers Down (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - Frump, Robert. Two Tankers Down (Box 340, Folder 11)
    - Frump, Robert. Until the Sea Shall Free Them: Life, Death, and Survival in The Merchant Marine (Box 340, Folder 12)
    - Frump, Robert. Until the Sea Shall Free Them: Life, Death, and Survival in the Merchant Marine (Box 340, Folder 13)
    - Frye, Northrop. The Great Code: The Bible and Literature (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Fugard, Lisa. Skinner's Drift (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth. The Great Crash, 1929 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth. The Scotch (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - Garbo, Norman and Howard Goodkind. Confrontation (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - Gardner, Gerald and Jim Bellow. Our Most Famous 80 Year Olds (Box 341, Folder 6)
    - Gardner, John W. Excellence (Box 341, Folder 7)
    - Gardner, John W. Excellence: Can We Be Equal and Excellent Too? (Box 341, Folder 8)
    - Gardner, John W. On Leadership (Box 341, Folder 9)
    - Gardner, John W. On Leadership (Box 341, Folder 10)
    - Gardner, John W. On Leadership (Box 341, Folder 11)
    - Gardner, John W. Self-Renewal (Box 341, Folder 12)
    - Gardner, John W. Self-Renewal: The Individual and the Innovative Society (Box 341, Folder 13)
    - Gavin, James M. Crisis Now (Box 341, Folder 14)
    - Gavin, James M. On to Berlin (Box 341, Folder 15)
    - Gent, Peter. The Conquering Heroes (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - Gent, Peter. The Franchise (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - Gent, Peter. The Last Magic Summer: A Season with My Son (Box 342, Folder 3)
    - Gent, Peter. The Last Magic Summer: A Season With My Son, A Memoir (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - Gent, Peter. North Dallas Forty (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - Gent, Peter. North Dallas After 40: A Sequel (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - Gent, Peter. Texas Celebrity Turkey Trot (Box 342, Folder 7)
    - Gibson, Althea. I Always Wanted to Be Somebody (Box 342, Folder 8)
    - Giollarnath, Sean Mac. Conamara (Box 342, Folder 9)
    - Gladwell, Malcolm. Blink (Box 342, Folder 10)
    - Glusman, John A. Conduct Under Fire: Four American Doctors and Their Fight for Life as Prisoners of the Japanese, 1941-1945 (Box 342, Folder 11)
    - Godowsky, Dagmar. First Person Plural: The Lives of Dagmar Godowsky (Box 342, Folder 12)
    - Goldman, Albert. Ladies and Gentlemen: Lenny Bruce!! (Box 342, Folder 13)
    - Goldstone, Lawrence and Nancy Goldstone. Slightly chipped: footnotes in booklore (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Golenbock, Peter. Bums: An Oral History of the Brooklyn Dodgers (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - Goodwin, Doris Kearns. The Fitzgeralds and the Kennedys (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - Goodwin, Richard N. The American Condition (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Goodwin, Richard N. Remembering America (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - Goodwin, Richard N. Remembering America: a Voice From the Sixties (Box 343, Folder 6)
    - Goodwin, Richard N. Triumph or Tragedy: Reflections on Vietnam (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - Goodwyn, Lawrence. Democratic Promise: The Populist Moment in America (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - Gordon, Mary. Seeing Through Places (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - Gornick, Vivian. The Solitude of Self: Thinking About Elizabeth Cady Stanton (Box 343, Folder 10)
    - Gowdy, Curt and Al Hirshberg. Cowboy at the Mike (Box 343, Folder 11)
    - Graham, Fred. The Alias Program (Box 343, Folder 12)
    - Graham, Fred. The Alias Program (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - Graham, Fred. Happy Talk: Confessions of a TV Newsman (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - Graham, Fred. Happy Talk: Confessions of a TV Newsman (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - Graham, Fred. The Self-Inflicted Wound (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - Graves, Ralph. Champagne Kisses, Cyanide Dreams (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - Graves, Ralph. Objects of Desire: A Portrait of Love and Marriage (Box 344, Folder 6)
    - Graves, Ralph. Objects of Desire: A Portrait of Love and Marriage (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - Graves, Ralph. Share of Honor (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - Green, Ted with Al Hirshberg. High Stick (Box 344, Folder 9)
    - Greene, Robert W. The Sting Man: Inside ABSCAM (Box 344, Folder 10)
    - Greenfield, Jeff. If Kennedy Lived: The First and Second Terms of President John F. Kennedy: An Alternate History (Box 344, Folder 11)
    - Greenfield, Jeff. Jeff Greenfield's Book of Books (Box 344, Folder 12)
    - Greenfield, Jeff. "Oh, Waiter One Order of Crow!" Inside the Strangest Presidential Election Finish in American History (Box 344, Folder 13)
    - Greenfield, Jeff. Playing to Win: An Insider's Guide to Politics (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Greenfield, Jeff. The Real Campaign: How the Media Missed the Story of the 1980 Campaign (Box 345, Folder 2)
    - Greenfield, Jeff. Tiny Giant: Nate Archibald (Box 345, Folder 3)
    - Gross, Jacquelyn. Make Your Child A Lifelong Reader (Box 345, Folder 4)
    - Gross, Leonard. The Last, Best Hope: Eduardo Frei and Chilean Democracy (Box 345, Folder 5)
    - Gross, Leonard. Mirror (Box 345, Folder 6)
    - Gross, Leonard. Strangers at the Gate (Box 345, Folder 7)
    - Grunwald, Michael. The New New Deal: The Hidden Story of Change in the Obama Era (Box 345, Folder 8)
    - Guthrie, Janet. Janet Guthrie: A Life at Full Throttle (Box 345, Folder 9)
    - Gutham, Edwon O. and Jeffrey Shulman. Robert Kennedy In His Own Words: The Unpublished Recollections of the Kennedy Years (Box 345, Folder 10)
    - Gutman, Herbert G. The Black Family in Slavery & Freedom, 1750-1925 (Box 345, Folder 11)
    - Hadley, Arthur T. The Invisible Primary, The Inside Story of the Other Presidential Race: The Making of the Candidate (Box 345, Folder 12)
    - Hadley, Arthur T. The Invisible Primary (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - Hadley, Arthur T. A Life in Order (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - Hadley, Arthur T. The Straw Giant (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Hagstrom, Jr., Robert G. The Warren Buffet Way: Investment Strategies of the World's Greatest Inventor (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - Halberstam, David. The Reckoning (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Hamill, Pete. Downtown: My Manhattan (Box 346, Folder 6)
    - Hample, Stuart. Blood for Holly Warner (Box 346, Folder 7)
    - Handlin, Oscar. This Was America (Box 346, Folder 8)
    - Hare, Cyril. Tragedy at Law (Box 346, Folder 9)
    - Harrelson, Ken and Al Hirshberg. Hawk (Box 346, Folder 10)
    - Hart, Matthew. Diamond: A Journey to the Heart of an Obsession (Box 346, Folder 11)
    - Haviaras, Stratis. Millenial Afterlives: A Retrospective (Box 346, Folder 12)
    - Haycraft, Howard and John Beecroft. Ten Great Mysteries (Box 347, Folder 1)
    - Haycraft, Howard and John Beecroft, Ed. A Treasury of Mysteries (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - Haycraft, Howard and John Beecroft. A Treasury of Great Mysteries, Volume 2 (Box 347, Folder 3)
    - Haynes, Connie, Eve Kraft and John Conroy. Speed, Strength, and Stamina: Conditioning for Tennis (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - Head, Edith. The Dress Doctor: Prescriptions for Style from A to Z (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - Head, Edith. How to Dress for Success (Box 347, Folder 6)
    - Heide, Robert and John Gilman. Greenwich Village: a primo guide to shopping, eating, and making merry in true Bohemia (Box 347, Folder 7)
    - Heller, Joseph. Catch-22 (Box 347, Folder 8)
    - Hemphill, Paul. The Ballad of Little River: A Tale of Race and Restless Youth in the Rural South (Box 347, Folder 9)